<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- CREATE IN THIS FORM AND ADD ARRAY TO INDEX!!!:
     <array name="CLUE_NAME">
        <item>TITLE</item>
        <item>DESCRIPTION

        </item>
        <item>SHORT DESCRIPTION OR SUMMARY</item>

        <item>TOKEN 1</item>
        <item>TOKEN 2</item>
        ...etc...
    </array>
    -->

    <!-- INDEX OF CLUES -->
    <array name="demo_clues_index">
        <item>@array/richard_clue1</item>
        <item>@array/richard_clue2</item>
        <item>@array/richard_clue3</item>
        <item>@array/richard_clue4</item>
        <item>@array/richard_clue7</item>
        <item>@array/richard_clue8</item>
        <item>@array/richard_clue9</item>
        <item>@array/richard_clue10</item>
        <item>@array/janet_clue1</item>
        <item>@array/janet_clue2</item>
        <item>@array/janet_clue3</item>
        <item>@array/janet_clue4</item>
        <item>@array/janet_clue5</item>
        <item>@array/janet_clue6</item>
        <item>@array/janet_clue7</item>
        <item>@array/janet_clue8</item>
        <item>@array/janet_clue9</item>
        <item>@array/marc_clue1</item>
        <item>@array/marc_clue2</item>
        <item>@array/marc_clue3</item>
        <item>@array/marc_clue4</item>
        <item>@array/marc_clue5</item>
    </array>

    <!-- Richard -->
    <array name="richard_clue1">
        <item>richard_clue1</item>
        <item>Gossip #1</item>
        <item>You are walking through the campus when nearby students’ chatter catches your ears.\n\n\"I’m so bad at Mathematical Analysis, I think I’m gonna fail. But Richard’s classes are so boring...\"\n\n\"[Professor Richard]? From what I’ve heard there is more than one way to get good grades from here. You should meet him in his office hours, take your wallet.\"\n\nIntriguing, but could there be truth to those rumours?</item>
        <item>Students gossip about selling grades.</item>
        <item>@string/suspect_richard</item>
        <item>@string/location_computer_room</item>
    </array>
    <array name="richard_clue2">
        <item>richard_clue2</item>
        <item>Blackmail note</item>
        <item>A handwritten note by Catherina:\n\n\"I don’t understand how you get people to still pay for your services,\ndon’t they understand how blackmail works?\n\nNo matter, I do.\n\nI also know how to prove what you’re doing.\"\n\nWho was this meant to?</item>
        <item>Blackmail material from victim to suspect.</item>
        <item>@string/suspect_richard</item>
    </array>
    <array name="richard_clue3">
        <item>richard_clue3</item>
        <item>Final exams</item>
        <item>You may not be the best student there ever was. But even so, it wouldnt take that much to notice that these exams are pretty bad.\nSome of the questions are not even answered, but they are still highly graded.\nStrange.\nWho is the lecturer responsible for [suspect 2 subject] again?</item>
        <item>Bad exams with good grades</item>
        <item>@string/suspect_richard</item>
    </array>
    <array name="richard_clue4">
        <item>richard_clue4</item>
        <item>Computer Room Logs</item>
        <item>You are walking through the campus when nearby students\’ chatter catches your ears.\n\n\”I’m so bad at Mathematical Analysis, I think I’m gonna fail. But Richard’s classes are so boring…\”\n\n\”[Professor Richard]? From what I\’ve heard there is more than one way to get good grades from here. You should meet him in his office hours, take your wallet.\”\n\n Intriguing. But could there be truth to those rumours?</item>
        <item>computer room  (logged in las night)</item>
        <item>@string/location_computer_room</item>
        <item>@string/weapon_laptop</item>
    </array>
    <array name="richard_clue7">
        <item>richard_clue7</item>
        <item>A talk with her peers</item>
        <item>Some casual conversation some of Catherines ‘s colleagues has revealed some information about her. Apparently she was a great student and aced all the classes she’d take. Some were a bit confused as to how she managed to get so many good grades on Richard’s course, as this last months she has spent all her time working on her other project and the course subjects were quite complicated.</item>
        <item>interview with a friend.</item>
        <item>@string/suspect_richard</item>
        <item>@string/location_workshop</item>
    </array>
    <array name="richard_clue8">
        <item>richard_clue8</item>
        <item>Enrollment plans</item>
        <item>You got a list with the courses that Catherine was taking this semester. An impressive list in size, it’s like she’s trying to do a whole year of studies in half the time. How could she manage doing so many at same time? You notice many of the courses are taught by Professor Richard</item>
        <item>enrollment on too many courses</item>
        <item>@string/suspect_richard</item>
    </array>
    <array name="richard_clue9">
        <item>richard_clue9</item>
        <item>Bent laptop</item>
        <item>You managed to have a quick check at Richard’s personal laptop! Unfortunately you are not able to get past his password protection, but you can’t help but notice a strange dent on the side of the laptop, as if it was used to bash someone’s head in. Could this possibly be the murder weapon??!!</item>
        <item>blunt weapon for teacher (laptop)</item>
        <item>@string/location_computer_room</item>
        <item>@string/suspect_richard</item>
        <item>@string/weapon_laptop</item>
    </array>
    <array name="richard_clue10">
        <item>richard_clue10</item>
        <item>Security camera access</item>
        <item>You try to get into the room where the controls for the security cameras are located. You can’t make it, at least not this time. You realize it would take a lot of work for someone that was not part of the university staff to be able to reach the room</item>
        <item>security cameras were turned off at the moment of crime </item>
        <item>@string/suspect_richard</item>
        <item>@string/suspect_janet</item>
    </array>

    <!-- Janet clues -->
    <array name="janet_clue1">
        <item>janet_clue1</item>
        <item>Toolbox</item>
        <item>Medium size toolbox, it has Catherina/’s name on it. Quite well supplied, she must have been spending a lot of time at the workshop.</item>
        <item>@string/location_workshop</item>
        <item>@string/weapon_hammer</item>
    </array>
    <array name="janet_clue2">
        <item>janet_clue2</item>
        <item>Victim/’s notebook</item>
        <item>This small notebook has some handwritten notes and sketches about a project the victim was working on. Apparently she was developing some kind of automated cleaning devices. Robotic janitors? Could be profitable, if it works.</item>
        <item>Notes about the project</item>
        <item>@string/location_workshop</item>
        <item>@string/weapon_robot_arm</item>
        <item>@string/suspect_janet</item>
    </array>
    <array name="janet_clue3">
        <item>janet_clue3</item>
        <item>Cleaning robot, alpha build</item>
        <item>This is the first prototype of the project on which Catherine was working so hard on. A humanoid cleaning robot. Apparently she has been working day and night on this project. It looks very effective. A piece of what would be its right arm is missing from the prototype</item>
        <item>prototype for the cleaning robo</item>
        <item>@string/location_workshop</item>
        <item>@string/weapon_robot_arm</item>
        <item>@string/suspect_janet</item>
    </array>
    <array name="janet_clue4">
        <item>janet_clue4</item>
        <item>Victimi/’s lab coat</item>
        <item>A bloodied lab coat was found on a bin near the school. The tag with the victim’s name is easily visible. The coat is completely covered in blood, as if it was used to clean the blood of the victim rather than if she was just wearing it when attacked. You wonder where are LAB coats usually kept?</item>
        <item>workshop where building robots (lab coat)</item>
        <item>@string/location_workshop</item>
        <item>@string/weapon_robot_arm</item>
        <item>@string/suspect_janet</item>
    </array>
    <array name="janet_clue5">
        <item>janet_clue5</item>
        <item>Cracked Broom</item>
        <item>There is a crack in this broom, apparently someone applied a strong force on it, possibly used it to hit someone. Could this be a murder weapon?</item>
        <item>blunt weapon from janitor</item>
        <item>@string/weapon_cracked_broom</item>
        <item>@string/suspect_janet</item>
    </array>
    <array name="janet_clue6">
        <item>janet_clue6</item>
        <item>A robot/’s right arm</item>
        <item>A large metal piece was found behind a bush in the university grounds. Apparently it’s a part from the prototype Catherine was building. How did it end up out of the workshop? Well, it is heavy and club-like. /“A good murder weapon as any/”, you think to yourself</item>
        <item>piece of the robot as a murder weapon</item>
        <item>@string/weapon_robot_arm</item>
        <item>@string/location_smoking_area</item>
        <item>@string/suspect_janet</item>
    </array>
    <array name="janet_clue7">
        <item>janet_clue7</item>
        <item>Catherine/’s Hammer</item>
        <item>A hammer was found misplaced in the campus, it belonged back in the workshop. It could be used as a murder weapon.</item>
        <item>@string/weapon_hammer</item>
        <item>@string/location_workshop</item>
    </array>
    <array name="janet_clue8">
        <item>janet_clue8</item>
        <item>Personnel Card</item>
        <item>An access card belonging to Janet, the janitor. Further investigation shows that she stayed late in the university on the night of the murder. Suspicious? Perhaps she was just cleaning…with a broom</item>
        <item>suspect number 3 stays longer on the night of the murder</item>
        <item>@string/weapon_cracked_broom</item>
        <item>@string/suspect_janet</item>
    </array>
    <array name="janet_clue9">
        <item>janet_clue9</item>
        <item>Bloody Sports Award</item>
        <item>This sport award is a bit dirty with blood, it could’ve been used as a murder weapon</item>
        <item>Award dyed in blood</item>
        <item>@string/weapon_award</item>
    </array>

    <!-- Marc -->
    <array name="marc_clue1">
        <item>marc_clue1</item>
        <item>Mobile Phone</item>
        <item>You found the mobile phone of the victim, one of the most recent messages caught your eye: /“This was fun while it lasted, but we’re done. I don’t want to see you anymore./” Was she breaking up with him through a text message? Cold</item>
        <item>Mobile phone with breakup SMS</item>
        <item>@string/suspect_marc</item>
    </array>
    <array name="marc_clue2">
        <item>marc_clue2</item>
        <item>Picture</item>
        <item>A picture of Catherina and Mark in the University’s open area, they look intimate. Perhaps they were more than just classmates?</item>
        <item>A picture of victim with suspect number 1</item>
        <item>Smoking Area</item>
        <item>@string/suspect_marc</item>
    </array>
    <array name="marc_clue3">
        <item>marc_clue3</item>
        <item>”Loving” picture</item>
        <item>You used your stealth skills and managed to get into the staff area in the campus. A quick peek into Janet’s personal belongings was enough for you to notice that she keeps a considerable amount of pictures of the student Marc at hand. Most of them were taken from the security cameras feed. Why would the school janitor keep those? Does she have a crush on him? Cute. Well, actually scratch that. Creepy!</item>
        <item>suspect 3 has pictures from suspect 1</item>
        <item>@string/suspect_janet</item>
    </array>
    <array name="marc_clue4">
        <item>marcu_clue4</item>
        <item>A pack of cigarettes</item>
        <item>You found a half filled cigarette pack among Catherine’s belongings. She must have slipped to the smoking area a few times during that night, it is a secluded area. Could that have been the murder scene?</item>
        <item>smoking area (pack of cigarettes)</item>
        <item>@string/location_smoking_area</item>
    </array>
    <array name="marc_clue5">
        <item>marc_clue5</item>
        <item>Social network status updates</item>
        <item>You had the great idea of checking the social network profiles of the people involved in the crime to see if you could get some clues. The first thing to jump your eyes is in Marc’s  profile, it says he was in a relationship with Catherine! A quick look in the victim’s profile is enough to see that she didn’t agree with that, as her relationship status is marked as /“single/”. Awkward</item>
        <item>social network relationship status (suspect 1)</item>
        <item>@string/suspect_marc</item>
        <item>@string/location_computer_room</item>
    </array>
</resources>